



CONTACT





gabaiz88@gmail.com





https://github.com/gabaiz88



LANGUAGES



- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- NODE.JS
- JAVA
- GITHUB
- SOL
- C#
- C++
- PHOTOSHOP

GABRIEL AIZMAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ANALYST **WEB DEVELOPER**

ABOUT

For 14 years I worked in positions related to the banking/financial industry. I worked as a Credit Risk Analyst, Bank Teller and Head Teller/Branch Operations Manager.

In 2022, I decided to leave my job and pursue my dream! In the last year I studied and trained in the IT area, by taking Web Development courses, as well as undertaking the Systems Analyst career in ORT Institute in Buenos Aires.



EXPERIENCE

-BANCO CREDICOOP COOP. LTDO.

Mar 2020 - Aug 2022

Head Teller / Branch Operations Manager

-BANCO CREDICOOP COOP, LTDO.

Jun 2014 - Mar 2020

Bank Teller

-METROPOLIS CIA. FINANCIERA

Dec 2012 - Jun 2014

Credit Risk Analyst

-METROPOLIS CIA. FINANCIERA

May 2010 - Dec 2012

Head Teller



EDUCATION

-ORT INSTITUTE ARGENTINA

Aug 2021 - Present

SYSTEMS ANALYST

-CODER HOUSE

Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

JAVASCRIPT

Aug 2022 - Oct 2022

WEB DEVELOPER